This Is Me…Now is a drama, music, documentary film directed by Dave Meyers.
An intimate, fantastical and narrative-driven reflection of Jennifer Lopez's journey of self-healing and self-love in an
immersive world where music and visuals intertwine, revealing the challenges faced and the triumphs achieved.
The Artist, played by Jennifer Lopez.
Rex Stone / Biker, played by Ben Affleck.
Flower Farmer, played by Idaliz Christian.
Therapist, played by Fat Joe.
The Cynic / Mike, played by Matthew Law.
The Lover, played by Brandon Delsid.
Now You See Me: Now You Don't is a 2025 American heist film directed by Ruben Fleischer from a screenplay by Michael Lesslie, the
writing duo of Paul Wernick and Rhett Reese, and Seth Grahame-Smith, based on a story by Eric Warren Singer and Lesslie.
The film is the sequel to  Now You See Me 2 (2016) and the third
installment in the  Now You See Me film series.
The cast includes Jesse Eisenberg, Woody Harrelson, Dave Franco, Isla Fisher, Lizzy Caplan, and Morgan Freeman returning from
previous films, joined by new cast members Justice Smith, Dominic Sessa, Ariana Greenblatt, and Rosamund Pike.
Now You See Me: Now You Don't premiered at the Harbour Club in Amsterdam, Netherlands, on November
11, 2025, and was released in the United States on November 14, 2025, by Lionsgate.
The film grossed $240 million worldwide and received mixed reviews from critics.
A sequel is in development.
The film explores themes of domestic violence,
companion piece, music documentary.
The tone is emotional.